Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Sweet Secrets=
=أسرار حلوة=
=Episode 17= (The Sweet Lie)
=الحلقة 17= (الكذبة الحلوة)
Yan.
نعم.
You're finally awake.
لقد استيقظت أخيرا.
How silly of you.
كم أنت غبي!
Why were you at the Nine Soul Bridge?
لماذا كنت في جسر النفوس التسعة؟
It was a bottomless abyss down there.
لقد كانت هناك هاوية بلا قاع.
If you fell, that'd be terrible.
إذا سقطت، فسيكون ذلك فظيعًا.
You've always protected me before.
لقد قمت بحمايتي دائمًا من قبل.
I wanted to protect you this time.
لقد أردت حمايتك هذه المرة.
You're my wife.
أنت زوجتي.
It's my duty to protect you.
من واجبي أن أحميك.
I just want to hold you like this.
أريد فقط أن أحتضنك هكذا.
All the time.
طوال الوقت.
I want to always be with you
أريد أن أكون معك دائمًا
and lead a peaceful life.
ويعيشون حياة سلمية.
Nothing
لا شئ
could ever separate us again.
لا يمكن أن يفصلنا مرة أخرى.
Not even death
ولا حتى الموت
could tear us apart.
قد يمزقنا.
Yes.
نعم.
We'll never be apart again.
لن نفترق مرة أخرى أبدًا.
Lu Huayan was able to reenter the dream and retrieve the Bodhi Fruit.
تمكن لو هوايان من العودة إلى الحلم واستعادة فاكهة بودي.
Did you help him?
هل ساعدته؟
(Li Motong) I helped Li Motong.
(لي موتونج) لقد ساعدت لي موتونج.
As the Supreme Priest of Wujian,
بصفته الكاهن الأعلى لـ Wujian،
I couldn't just stand by and watch the Lord of Wujian
لم أستطع أن أقف مكتوف الأيدي وأشاهد سيد ووجيان
suffer from the Heart-Devouring Curse.
أعاني من لعنة التهام القلب.
He brought all of this upon himself!
لقد جلب كل هذا على نفسه!
If he had followed the plan,
لو أنه اتبع الخطة،
he wouldn't be suffering like this.
لن يعاني مثل هذا.
Due to what he did,
بسبب ما فعله،
even the Soul-Eating Sword is gone now.
حتى سيف أكل الروح قد ذهب الآن.
Tell me. What do we do now?
أخبرني ماذا نفعل الآن؟
I'm willing to sacrifice all my power
أنا على استعداد للتضحية بكل قوتي
to reforge the sword's soul.
لإعادة تشكيل روح السيف.
For real?
لريال مدريد؟
When that time comes,
عندما يأتي ذلك الوقت،
the Soul-Eating Sword infused with all my power
السيف آكل الروح المشبع بكل قوتي
will be even stronger than before.
ستكون أقوى من ذي قبل.
We'll no longer need to wait until the night of the Crimson Moon.
لن نحتاج بعد الآن إلى الانتظار حتى ليلة القمر القرمزي.
You're sacrificing so much
أنت تضحي بالكثير
just to keep Li Motong alive, aren't you?
فقط لإبقاء لي موتونغ على قيد الحياة، أليس كذلك؟
It's been hundreds of years
لقد مرت مئات السنين
and you still love him.
ومازلت تحبه.
Three days from now,
بعد ثلاثة أيام من الآن،
the Soul-Eating Sword will be complete.
سيف أكل الروح سيكون كاملا.
We'll decide what to do then.
سوف نقرر ماذا نفعل حينها.
See your way out.
انظر إلى طريقك للخروج.
So that's how it is.
هكذا هو الأمر.
He's a fool.
إنه أحمق.
So are you.
وأنت كذلك.
Yan, we're done for the day.
يان، لقد انتهينا لهذا اليوم.
Today's rehearsal went really well.
لقد كانت بروفة اليوم جيدة جدًا.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكرا لك على عملك الجاد.
I'll off.
سأذهب.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Lu Huayan.
لو هوايان.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why can I never surpass you?
لماذا لا أستطيع أن أتفوق عليك أبدًا؟
Why are you always ahead of me?
لماذا أنت دائما متقدما علي؟
No matter how hard I try,
بغض النظر عن مدى جهدي،
why do you always manage to steal my limelight?
لماذا تنجح دائمًا في سرقة الأضواء مني؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Gu Meng.
قو منغ.
You're nothing but Jing Haisi's lapdog.
أنت لست سوى كلب جينغ هايسي.
Haven't you heard the saying "you are who you surround yourself with"?
هل سمعت المثل القائل "أنت من تحيط نفسك به"؟
I was lenient enough to have kicked you out of the Paramount.
لقد كنت متساهلاً بما فيه الكفاية لطردك من باراماونت.
Lu Huayan, you're wrong.
لو هوايان، أنت مخطئ.
I'm no longer the Gu Meng I used to be.
أنا لم أعد Gu Meng الذي كنت عليه سابقًا.
Now, not only can I disfigure you,
الآن، ليس بإمكاني تشويهك فحسب،
but I can also take your life
ولكن يمكنني أيضًا أن آخذ حياتك
as easily as crushing an ant.
بسهولة مثل سحق نملة.
You think you're worthy of being part of Wujian?
هل تعتقد أنك تستحق أن تكون جزءًا من Wujian؟
I'll take back your Wujian force right now.
سأستعيد قوة Wujian الخاصة بك الآن.
I don't care about others,
لا يهمني الآخرين
but don't you dare touch what's mine!
ولكن لا تجرؤ على لمس ما هو لي!
Li Motong!
لي موتونغ!
I am
أنا أكون
yours?
لك؟
You belong to Wujian.
أنت تنتمي إلى Wujian.
I don't mind having another helper.
لا مانع لدي من وجود مساعد آخر.
Yet from now on,
ولكن من الآن فصاعدا،
don't interfere in human affairs.
لا تتدخل في شؤون البشر.
But I joined Wujian
لكنني انضممت إلى Wujian
to help you with your work.
لمساعدتك في عملك.
Like I said,
كما قلت،
stay out
ابقى خارجا
of Wujian's business.
من أعمال Wujian.
(The Wujian force grows weaker by the day.)
(قوة Wujian تصبح أضعف يوما بعد يوم.)
(I must find another way.)
(يجب أن أجد طريقة أخرى.)
Darling.
محبوب.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
Are you hiding something from me?
هل تخفي عني شيئا؟
What could I possibly be hiding from you?
ماذا يمكن أن أخفيه عنك؟
With your power,
مع قوتك،
how could you have lost to Jing Haisi?
كيف يمكنك أن تخسر أمام جينغ هايسي؟
Is the backlash from the Mei pearl getting worse?
هل تتفاقم ردة الفعل الناجمة عن لؤلؤة مي ؟
Did the Bodhi Fruit not work?
هل لم تنجح فاكهة بودي؟
You're overthinking.
أنت تفكر كثيرًا.
Everyone slips up sometimes.
الجميع يخطئ في بعض الأحيان.
Don't be so on edge.
لا تكن متوتراً جداً.
But Miss You and Jing Haisi said
لكن ملكة جمال يو وجينغ هايسي قالتا
that you'll die if you don't take back the Mei pearl.
أنك ستموت إذا لم تستعيد لؤلؤة مي.
Yet you told me that as long as you ate the Bodhi Fruit,
ومع ذلك قلت لي أنه طالما أكلت فاكهة بودي،
you'd be fine.
سوف تكون بخير.
Don't worry, darling.
لا تقلقي يا عزيزتي.
I'm really fine.
أنا بخير حقا.
Right now, what matters most
في الوقت الحالي، ما هو الأكثر أهمية
is You Zimei actually gave Gu Meng inhuman powers.
هل يو زيمي هو من أعطى قو منغ قوى غير إنسانية؟
It's not safe for you to go out alone.
ليس من الآمن لك الخروج بمفردك.
For now,
في الوقت الراهن،
don't go to the Paramount.
لا تذهب إلى باراماونت.
Are you sure you're all right?
هل أنت متأكد أنك بخير؟
Yes, darling. I'm fine.
نعم عزيزتي، أنا بخير.
Alright, then.
حسنا إذن.
I can't do anything with you.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء معك.
I'll ask Lan for some time off
سأطلب من لان بعض الوقت للراحة
to take care of you.
لرعايتك.
Who's taking care of whom here?
من يهتم بمن هنا؟
Things are dangerous right now.
الأمور خطيرة الآن.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you have to stay by my side at all times.
يتوجب عليك البقاء بجانبي في جميع الأوقات.
If we're always together like this,
إذا كنا دائما معا مثل هذا،
your subordinates will start teasing you.
سيبدأ مرؤوسوك بمضايقتك.
They'd call you a maniac who dotes on his wife.
سيطلقون عليك لقب المجنون الذي يحب زوجته.
A maniac who dotes on his wife?
مجنون يحب زوجته؟
I actually like the sound of that.
أنا في الواقع أحب هذا الصوت.
It's sweet as honey.
إنه حلو مثل العسل.
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪